The Order 1886 [Is] the Best Looking game ever Made and Probably
Ever will Be Made but it's only About 40 minutes Long so can't really be Called the best game of all Time
so the game Starts With the Main Character being Underwater he Sports There were These Two red Clothes Guys
So far We aren't Really Sure if These two guys Are his Bros and this Is just a prank but then
We see Prison Bars so now We know Maybe the tour here has Decided that This isn't fun Anymore?
So he Kind of leaves
Then He's on Top of the Building and There are These People everywhere and They're Screaming at
Him then he um sink to the icy Water and he dies
Turns out it was only A flash Forward, so he Plays This Guy Named Galahad he Seen A club Called the order he
Also has A very Fancy Mustache and very Fancy Clothing [the] game is Set in The Fictional City of
London and Thus The Name implies it's
Also delayed
1800s so everything Is Sad and Dark and Smoky and Whatnot so
Galahad or Grayson as he likes to be [called] is a member of the knights of the Round table it's a group created to fight
Werewolves and Protect Humanity but They, don't actually Call them where Once They, Call them lichens why
Because the order are a Bunch of Pretentious Wankers
We find out that the order was Created by King Arthur yes?
That Doors Dude The Guy That [Pulls] sort of this Stone and then became a fish and then
Swam around With Merlin yeah you know you know the Guy so only he got
Really Drunk and Walked Into Lancelot [Sophos] boil and See I was Shagging this Bird Yeah and I was Thinking a firm that Kills?
Werewolves Good Idea in it [prov] in Addition you wanna go
Mate A fucking Shank yeah and that's the official Backstory so [the] People in your aren't Actually allowed to die of Old age because Apparently
Teaching A, werewolf Killer Takes Way longer Than its normal Doctorate so they have this Black Drink Made from
The Holy Grail and They Drink from it and it will Stay Younger Forever no not Really, on but They Grow
Much slower But They Still Act the Same way they Look There Can only be two Reasons for this one
People Sorta Treat Them the way they, Look so they never Really Develop Two and Way more likely
The drink Makes you an Idiot
But you Know Because of the Old age Can the evens Itself out so you get Smarter but the same Time you get dumber Because
You Drink it yeah you know, what I mean They?
Don't only Fight werewolves There's also a rebellion going on why Were They Rebelling
[I] don't know I don't care the thing Is when There's like A
Historical Setting There's Always Someone Rebelling About something to be Completely Honest I'm [not] even Sure
They Were Rebelling They Said That Because I've Been on?
Several Different Spanish Islands and I met Enough British People to Say that that's Just how, they are the game has two major Problems
When A friend told me About this game he Said that
Well They're Making Game [it] has Wearables in It and it's Third-Person?
so
No I kind of Assumed that it was a romance
Game [I] guess When I hear Where was I kind of Assumed yeah it's a romance game Obviously but
I was very Disappointed when it was an Action game Just Sad and the other Thing Is I don't really find the late
18-Hundreds very Fascinating or magical ring Interesting at all I know that some People they go
Mad About the Victorian Era that's Amazing I'm not one of them
I, was much Preferred if the game was set in The more Magical and
Historical Year
1986 Looking Up at, Galahad Just go and Watch Top gun
Then The order Could Have Been Shot down Because some Margaret Thatcher [it] Would Have Been an Amazing game but Sadly
We're Stuck in This Stupid Time Period but you know other than Those Two things I really think that the organ is a great
Movie [if] You're interested [You] [Should] Check out Another Review and that's the Killian Experience
Hmm go tommy lose your!
like Subscribe
This Is just great Greek Salad
Mmm
Anyways Next Review
Would Probably Be out Tonight Two Weeks?
And before Would be longer be like 10 minutes or something
[Distributed] Forever To Make but net next One Really even Long as, you Take given Long to Make